Someone's always watching.
The Night Clerk is a thriller, crime, drama film directed by Michael Cristofer.
Hotel night clerk Bart Bromley is a highly
intelligent young man on the Autism spectrum.
When a woman is murdered during his shift, Bart becomes the prime suspect.
As the police investigation closes in, Bart makes a personal connection with a beautiful guest named
Andrea, but soon realises he must stop the real murderer before she becomes the next victim.
Bart Bromley, played by Tye Sheridan.
Andrea Rivera, played by Ana de Armas.
Detective Espada, played by John Leguizamo.
Ethel Bromley, played by Helen Hunt.
Karen Perretti, played by Jacque Gray.
Nick Perretti, played by Johnathon Schaech.
The Night Clerk is a 2020 American crime drama film,
written and directed by Michael Cristofer.
It stars Tye Sheridan, Ana de Armas, John Leguizamo and Helen Hunt, and follows a
hotel night clerk who becomes the center of a murder investigation.
The film was released on February 21, 2020, by Saban Films.
On June 6, 2020, Netflix released the film on its platform.
The film explores themes of hotel, falsely accused,
murder, surveillance camera, autistic.
The tone is emotional and intense.